<resources>
	<string name="Alms_name">Alms</string>
	<string name="Alms_desc">Once per turn: If you have no Treasures in play, gain a card costing up to 4 Coin.</string>
	<string name="Borrow_name">Borrow</string>
	<string name="Borrow_desc">+1 Buy\nOnce per turn: If your -1 Card token isn\'t on your deck, put it there and +1 Coin.</string>
	<string name="Quest_name">Quest</string>
	<string name="Quest_desc">You may discard an Attack, two Curses, or six cards. If you do , gain a Gold.</string>
	<string name="Save_name">Save</string>
	<string name="Save_desc">+1 Buy\nOnce per turn: Set aside a card from your hand, and put it into your hand at end of turn (after drawing).</string>
	<string name="ScoutingParty_name">Scouting Party</string>
	<string name="ScoutingParty_desc">+1 Buy\nLook at the top 5 cards of your deck. Discard 3 of them and put the rest back in any order.</string>
	<string name="TravellingFair_name">Travelling Fair</string>
	<string name="TravellingFair_desc">+2 Buys\nWhen you gain a card this turn, you may put it on top of your deck.</string>
	<string name="Bonfire_name">Bonfire</string>
	<string name="Bonfire_desc">Trash up to 2 cards you have in play.</string>
	<string name="Expedition_name">Expedition</string>
	<string name="Expedition_desc">Draw 2 extra cards for your next hand.</string>
	<string name="Ferry_name">Ferry</string>
	<string name="Ferry_desc">Move your -2 Cost token to an Action Supply pile (cards from that pile cost 2 Coin less on your turns, but not less than 0 Coin).</string>
	<string name="Plan_name">Plan</string>
	<string name="Plan_desc">Move your Trashing token to an Action Supply pile (when you buy a card from that pile, you may trash a card from your hand).</string>
	<string name="Mission_name">Mission</string>
	<string name="Mission_desc">Once per turn: If the previous turn wasn\'t yours, take another turn after this one, in which you can\'t buy cards.</string>
	<string name="Pilgrimage_name">Pilgrimage</string>
	<string name="Pilgrimage_desc">Once per turn: Turn your Journey token over; then if it\'s face up, choose up to 3 differently named cards you have in play and gain a copy of each.</string>
	<string name="Ball_name">Ball</string>
	<string name="Ball_desc">Take your -1 Coin token. Gain 2 cards each costing up to 4 Coin.</string>
	<string name="Raid_name">Raid</string>
	<string name="Raid_desc">Gain a silver per silver you have in play. Each other player puts this -1 Card token on his deck.</string>
	<string name="Seaway_name">Seaway</string>
	<string name="Seaway_desc">Gain an Action card costing up to 4 Coin. Move your +1 Buy token to its pile.</string>
	<string name="Trade_name">Trade</string>
	<string name="Trade_desc">Trash up to 2 cards from your hand. Gain a silver per card you trashed.</string>
	<string name="LostArts_name">Lost Arts</string>
	<string name="LostArts_desc">Move your +1 Action token to an Action supply pile.</string>
	<string name="Training_name">Training</string>
	<string name="Training_desc">Move your +1 Coin token to an Action supply pile.</string>
	<string name="Inheritance_name">Inheritance</string>
	<string name="Inheritance_desc">Once per game: Set aside a non-Victory Action card from the supply costing up to 4 Coin. Move your Estate token to it.</string>
	<string name="Pathfinding_name">Pathfinding</string>
	<string name="Pathfinding_desc">Move your +1 Card token to an Action supply pile.</string>
</resources>
