<resources>
	<string name="Aqueduct_name">Aqueduct</string>
	<string name="Aqueduct_desc">When you gain a Treasure, move 1 Victory token from its pile to this. When you gain a Victory card, take the Victory token from this.\nSetup: Put 8 Victory tokens on the Silver and Gold pile.</string>
	<string name="Arena_name">Arena</string>
	<string name="Arena_desc">At the start of your Buy phase, you may discard an Action card. If you do, take 2 Victory tokens from here.\nSetup: Put 6 Victory tokens here per player.</string>
	<string name="BanditFort_name">Bandit Fort</string>
	<string name="BanditFort_desc">When scoring, -2 Victory points for each Silver and each Gold you have.</string>
	<string name="Basilica_name">Basilica</string>
	<string name="Basilica_desc">When you buy a card, if you have 2 coin or more left, take 2 Victory tokens from here.\nSetup: Put 6 Victory tokens here per player.</string>
	<string name="Baths_name">Baths</string>
	<string name="Baths_desc">When you end your turn without having gained a card, take 2 Victory tokens from here.\nSetup: Put 6 Victory tokens here per player.</string>
	<string name="Battlefield_name">Battlefield</string>
	<string name="Battlefield_desc">When you gain a Victory card, take 2 Victory tokens from here.\nSetup: Put 6 Victory tokens here per player.</string>
	<string name="Colonnade_name">Colonnade</string>
	<string name="Colonnade_desc">When you buy an Action card, if you have a copy of it in play,  take 2 Victory tokens from here.\nSetup: Put 6 Victory tokens here per player.</string>
	<string name="DefiledShrine_name">Defiled Shrine</string>
	<string name="DefiledShrine_desc">When you gain an Action, move 1 Victory token from its pile to this. When you buy a curse, take the Victory tokens from this.\nSetup: Put 2 Victory tokens on each non-Gathering supply pile.</string>
	<string name="Fountain_name">Fountain</string>
	<string name="Fountain_desc">When scoring, +15 Victory points if you have at least 10 Coppers.</string>
	<string name="Keep_name">Keep</string>
	<string name="Keep_desc">When scoring, +5 Victory points per differently named Treasure you have, that you have more copies of than each other player, or tied for most.</string>
	<string name="Labyrinth_name">Labyrinth</string>
	<string name="Labyrinth_desc">When you gain a 2nd card in one of your turns,  take 2 Victory tokens from here.\nSetup: Put 6 Victory tokens here per player.</string>
	<string name="MountainPass_name">Mountain Pass</string>
	<string name="MountainPass_desc">When you are the first player to gain a Province, after that turn, each player bids once, up to 40 Debt, ending with you. High bidder gets 8 Victory tokens and takes the Debt they bid.</string>
	<string name="Museum_name">Museum</string>
	<string name="Museum_desc">When scoring, +2 Victory points per differently named card you have.</string>
	<string name="Obelisk_name">Obelisk</string>
	<string name="Obelisk_desc">When scoring, +2 Victory points per card you have from the chosen pile.\nSetup: Choose a random Action supply pile.</string>
	<string name="Orchard_name">Orchard</string>
	<string name="Orchard_desc">When scoring, +4 Victory points per differently named Action card you have 3 or more copies of.</string>
	<string name="Palace_name">Palace</string>
	<string name="Palace_desc">When scoring, +3 Victory points per set you have of Copper-Silver-Gold.</string>
	<string name="Tomb_name">Tomb</string>
	<string name="Tomb_desc">When you trash a card, +1 Victory token.</string>
	<string name="Tower_name">Tower</string>
	<string name="Tower_desc">When scoring, +1 Victory point per non-Victory card you have from an empty Supply pile.</string>
	<string name="TriumphalArch_name">Triumphal Arch</string>
	<string name="TriumphalArch_desc">When scoring, +3 Victory point per copy you have of the 2nd most common Action card among your cards. (if it\'s a tie, count either).</string>
	<string name="Wall_name">Wall</string>
	<string name="Wall_desc">When scoring, -1 Victory points per card you have after the first 15.</string>
	<string name="WolfDen_name">Wolf Den</string>
	<string name="WolfDen_desc">When scoring, -3 Victory points per card you have exactly one copy of.</string>
</resources>
